Your
anxiety
never
actually
goes
away,
does
it?
Even
when
lives
going
good,
you're
still
anxious
about
something.
I
totally
get
it.
I
used
to
think
anxiety
was
about
external
stuff,
money
problems,
relationship
drama,
career
stress.
But
I
became
a
monk
and
realized
something
deep.
Anxiety
isn't
really
about
what's
happening
around
you.
It's
about
not
knowing
who
you
actually
are.
When
you
think
you're
just
this
random
body
in
a
meaningless
universe,
of
course
you're
gonna
be
anxious.
Everything
feels
scary
and
urgent
because
you
think
this
is
all
you
get.
But
you're
not
this
body.
You're
an
eternal
soul
and
your
natural
state
is
to
love
Krishna.
When
you
don't
know
this,
it's
like
having
amnesia
and
trying
to
navigate
life
without
knowing
your
own
identity.
That's
terrifying,
right?
Your
anxiety
is
basically
your
soul
saying,
I
don't
know
who
I
am
or
what
I'm
supposed
to
be
doing
here.
When
you
start
understanding
your
meant
to
serve
Krishna,
anxiety
naturally
decreases
because
you
have
this
unshakable
foundation.
You're
not
just
some
random
organism
trying
to
survive.
You're
a
beloved
soul
with
an
eternal
purpose.